Mather, John J.; Papers apap107
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
John J. Mather Papers
1965-1996
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap107
12 cubic ft.
Papers written by John J. Mather from 1965 to 1996.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives by Marilyn Mather in 2000.
Biographical Sketch
John J. Mather was a public servant who held a number of positions with the State University of New York (SUNY) Central Administration. Born in 1922 in Rolfe, Iowa, Mather served in the Navy during World War II. He worked for twelve years as a high school social studies teacher and later served as secretary to the African American Institute in New York City before joining the staff of the SUNY system during the mid-1960s. Mather began his career at SUNY as one of several assistants to the Chancellor. During the late 1960s, he was involved in efforts to document and understand student unrest on the various SUNY campuses. In 1971, Mather was promoted to the position of Executive Assistant to the Chancellor. In this position he participated in the establishment of the Empire State Youth Theatre Institute, helped organized a student exchange program with Russia, oversaw a major study of the economic impact of the SUNY system, and served as the Chancellor's representative during the conversion of the Delaware & Hudson Building in downtown Albany into a headquarters for SUNY Central. In 1978, Mather became Associate Chancellor for Continuing Education and Public Service, a position he would hold until 1984. During this time he oversaw the establishment and expansion of the New York Network, SUNY's public television production studio.
In 1984, Mather became the Administrator of the SUNY System Business Development Services Office. Here he was responsible for creating and overseeing several programs in which the various SUNY campuses collaborated with the private sector to encourage the economic development of New York State. The Small Business Development Center (SBDC) assisted small business owners, while the SUNY Business and Industry Centers (initially referred to as Development Centers for Business) provided research, training and technical support to businesses of all sizes, including national and multinational businesses looking to expand their operations in New York State. The Export New York program, meanwhile, encouraged New York State businesses to export to countries outside the United States.
After retiring from the SUNY system in 1990, Mather became the president of Rolfe, Inc., a private consulting company which worked on establishing trade links between America and Europe. During this period Mather helped establish a sister cities program which facilitated cultural and business exchanges between Albany and Tula, Russia and Ghent, Belgium. In the mid-1990s Mather was also active in a campaign to prevent Governor Pataki from cutting the SUNY budget. He died in 2000.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains 12 cu. ft. of substantial records from Mather's service as a SUNY administrator. The collection contains Mather's vast correspondence with colleagues and constituents as Assistant to the SUNY Chancellor (1965-1971), Executive Assistant to the Chancellor (1971-1978) and Associate Chancellor for Public Service (1978-1984).
The collection is divided into four series. Series 1: Correspondence (1966-1990) contains blue carbon copies of Mather's correspondence from throughout his career. This includes routine administrative correspondence as well as letters and memoranda to other SUNY administrators and to the Chancellor. It includes complete correspondence files for the years 1967, 1970 through 1972, 1977 through 1978 and 1981 through 1984 as well as partial correspondence files for the years 1966, 1968 and 1990.
Series 2: SUNY Administrative (1965-1996) contains materials related to the general administration of the State University of New York (SUNY), largely but not exclusively dating from John Mather's service as Assistant to the Chancellor (1965-1971), Executive Assistant to the Chancellor (1971-1978) and Associate Chancellor for Public Service (1978-1984). Series 2 is divided into 4 subseries. Subseries 1: Campus Unrest (1967-1973) contains files related to student unrest on the various SUNY campuses during the late 1960s and early 1970s. This subseries is arranged alphabetically by name of campus and/or by subject matter. Nearly all of the SUNY campuses experienced some form of student unrest during this period, and several, most notably SUNY Stony Brook, experienced large-scale disruption due to riots and protests. Subseries 2: New York Network (1975-1991) contains records related to New York Network, the public-access television studio run by the State University system. Subseries 3: Subject File (1969-1996) contains subject files related to a wide variety of topics, most notably the Empire State Youth Theatre Institute and the Russian exchange student program. It is organized alphabetically by subject. Subseries 4: SUNY Publications (1965-1995) contains publications of the State University of New York central administration, including annual reports, periodicals and related documents. Many different publication series are represented in this subseries, although none of them are complete.
Series 3: SUNY System Business Development Services (1981-1995) contains material related to Mather's service as administrator of this department and the various programs which he oversaw there. It is divided into four subseries, including a general subject file and subseries on the three main programs of the Business Development Services Office: the Small Business Development Center, the Business and Industry Centers, and Export New York.
Series 4: Rolfe, Inc. (1989-1996) contains material related to the private consulting firm which Mather ran following his retirement from the SUNY system.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1: Correspondence, 1966-1990
Series 2: SUNY Administrative Records, 1965-1996
Series 3: SUNY System Business Development Services, 1981-1995
Series 4: Rolfe, Inc., 1989-1996
State University of New York SUNY, Central Administration; Public Servants; Military and Armed Conflict; Education; Business and Industry; Architecture; African Americans and Civil Rights Organizations; Public policy; Public service commissions; State universities and colleges; Albany (N.Y.); Public Affairs and Policy; John J. Mather
- Correspondence, 1966-1990; 1; 2.5 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  Arranged chronologically, this series contains blue carbon copies of Mather's correspondence, including routine administrative correspondence as well as letters and memoranda to other SUNY administrators and to the Chancellor. It includes complete correspondence files for the years 1967, 1970 through 1972, 1977 through 1978 and 1981 through 1984 as well as partial correspondence files for the years 1966, 1968 and 1990. The series is arranged in chronological order.
  - Correspondence, January-February 1966 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, March 1966 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, April 1966 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, May 1966 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, June 1966 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1967 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, March-April 1967 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, May-June 1967 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, July-September 1967 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, October 1967 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, November-December 1967 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, August-September 1968 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, October-December 1968 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, January 1970 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, February-April 1970 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, May-June 1970 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, August-September 1970 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, October-December 1970 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1971 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, March-April 1971 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, May-June 1971 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, July-September 1971 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, October-December 1971 (Box 1 (1-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, January-April 1972 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, May-August 1972 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, September-December 1972 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, January-April 1977 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, May-July 1977 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, August-September 1977 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, October-December 1977 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1978 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, March-April 1978 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, May-June 1978 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, July 1978 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, August-December 1978 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, January-March 1981 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, April-June 1981 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, July-August 1981 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, September-October 1981 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, November-December 1981 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, January-March 1982 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, April-June 1982 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, July-October 1982 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, November-December 1982 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, January-March 1983 (Box 2 (1-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, April-June 1983 (Box 3 (1-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, July-August 1983 (Box 3 (1-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, September-October 1983 (Box 3 (1-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, November-December 1983 (Box 3 (1-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, January 1984 (Box 3 (1-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, February-March 1984 (Box 3 (1-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, April 1984 (Box 3 (1-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, May-June 1984 (Box 3 (1-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, July-December 1984 (Box 3 (1-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1990 (Box 3 (1-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, March-May 1990 (Box 3 (1-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, June-August 1990 (Box 3 (1-Correspondence), Folder 12)
- Series II:SUNY Administrative Records, 1965-1996; 2
  This series consists of records related to the SUNY Central Administration outside of the Business Development Services Office. The majority of records date from Mather's service as Assistant to the Chancellor, Executive Assistant to the Chancellor and [Vice Chancellor for Public Services. Series 2 is divided into four sub-series:
  - Campus Unrest, 1967-1973; 2.1
    - Albany, 1968 (Box 3 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 13)
    - Albany, 1969-1970 (Box 3 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 14)
    - Binghamton, 1968-1970 (Box 3 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 15)
    - Binghamton, 1969-1970 (Box 3 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 16)
    - Brockport, 1969-1970 (Box 3 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 17)
    - Buffalo, 1969-1970 (Box 3 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 18)
    - Buffalo, 1969-1970 (Box 3 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 19)
    - Buffalo, 1970 (Box 3 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 20)
    - Cobleskill, 1969-1972 (Box 3 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 21)
    - Damage Reports, 1970 (Box 3 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 22)
    - Four-Year, Agricultural and Technical Colleges, 1970 (Box 3 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 23)
    - Four-Year, Agricultural and Technical Colleges, 1970 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 1)
    - General, 1968-1969 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 2)
    - General, 1968-1970 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 3)
    - General, 1968-1970 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 4)
    - General, 1970 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 5)
    - General, 1970-1972 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 6)
    - General & Notes, Undated (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 7)
    - Insurgency Reports, 1970 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 8)
    - Insurgency Reports, 1970 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 9)
    - Lierheimer Memorandum, 1970 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 10)
    - News Clippings, 1968-1970 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 11)
    - News Clippings, 1970 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 12)
    - New Paltz, 1969 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 13)
    - New Paltz Report on President Neumaier, 1970 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 14)
    - New Paltz Report on President Neumaier, 1970 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 15)
    - Periodicals, 1969-1970 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 16)
    - Quick Response Manual, Undated (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 17)
    - Reports from Other (Non-SUNY) Universities, 1970; Undated (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 18)
    - State Police, 1968-1970 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 19)
    - Stony Brook, 1968-1969 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 20)
    - Stony Brook, 1967-1973 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 21)
    - Stony Brook Cahn Report, 1969 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 22)
    - Stony Brook Drug Raid, 1969 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 23)
    - Stony Brook Hearings, 1967-1969 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 24)
    - Stony Brook Hearings, 1967-1970 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 25)
    - Stony Brook Hearings, 1968-1970 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 26)
    - Stony Brook Police Raids, 1968 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 27)
    - Stony Brook Police Raids, 1968 (Box 4 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 28)
    - Stony Brook Police Raids, 1969 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 1)
    - Stony Brook Police Raids, 1969 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 2)
    - Stony Brook Police Raids Newsprint Clippings, 1969 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 3)
    - Stony Brook Security, 1969-1972 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 4)
    - Stony Brook Security, 1969-1972 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 5)
    - Students for a Democratic Society (SDS), 1968-1971 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 6)
    - Surveys, 1969-1970 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 7)
    - Surveys, 1969-1970 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 8)
    - Temporary State Commission to Study the Causes of Campus Unrest (Henderson Commission), 1969-1973 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 9)
    - Temporary State Commission to Study the Causes of Campus Unrest (Henderson Commission), 1969-1973 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 10)
    - Temporary State Commission to Study the Causes of Campus Unrest (Henderson Commission), 1969-1973 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 11)
  - New York Network, 1975-1991; 2.2
    - Bostain, James, 1982 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 12)
    - Buchman, Herman, 1981 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 13)
    - Buchman, Herman, 1981 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 14)
    - Buchman, Herman, 1981 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 15)
    - Interaudiovisuel Paris / Foresta Proposal, 1981-1982 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 16)
    - Javits, Jacob, 1982-1984 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 17)
    - Kennedy Event, 1984 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 18)
    - Logo Options, 1982 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 19)
    - Modumath (series), 1975-1984 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 20)
    - Olympics, 1979-1984 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 21)
    - Policy Committee, 1976-1980 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 22)
    - Rate Schedules, 1981-1984 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 23)
    - Services and Contracts with Private Industry, 1979-1985 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 24)
    - Services and Contracts with State Agencies, 1977-1980 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 25)
    - Services and Contracts with State Agencies, 1981-1985 (Box 5 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 25)
    - Southern Tier Docu-Promo, 1982-1984 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 1)
    - Telecommunications, 1980-1981 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 2)
    - Telecommunications, 1980-1982 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 3)
    - Telecommunications, 1981-1982 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 4)
    - Telecommunications, 1981-1984 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 5)
    - Telecommunications, 1982-1984 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 6)
    - Teleconferencing, 1979-1984 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 7)
    - Teleproduction Department, Undated (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 8)
    - Television, 1978-1980 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 9)
    - Television, 1980-1982 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 10)
    - Television, 1980-1982 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 11)
    - Television, 1982-1984 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 12)
    - Travel, 1982-1984 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 13)
    - Trustee Presentation, 1977-1980 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 14)
    - Video Production Pending, 1984 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 15)
    - WAMC, 1982 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 16)
    - White House Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 17)
  - Subject File, 1969-1996; 2.3
    - Chancellor's Innovating Fund, 1971-1972 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 18)
    - "Command and Control at Emergency Incidents" (Conference at SUNY-Binghamton), 1983 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 19)
    - Council on International Business, 1980 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 20)
    - Council on International Business, 1980-1981 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 21)
    - Council on International Business, 1981-1983 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 22)
    - Dedication of the Egg, 1977-1981 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 23)
    - Du Mond, Arlene, 1969-1970 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 24)
    - Economic Impact Studies, 1969-1979 (Box 6 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 25)
    - Economic Impact Study, 1972-1973 (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 1)
    - Economic Impact Study, 1972-1973 (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 2)
    - Empire State College, 1970-1971 (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 3)
    - Empire State College, 1971-1973 (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 4)
    - Empire State College Oral History Project, 1989-1991 (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 5)
    - Empire State Youth Theatre Institute, 1974-1975 (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 6)
    - Empire State Youth Theatre Institute, 1976-1977 (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 7)
    - Empire State Youth Theatre Institute Proposal, 1977 (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 8)
    - Empire State Youth Theatre Institute, 1977-1978 (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 9)
    - Empire State Youth Theatre Institute, 1977-1978 (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 10)
    - Empire State Youth Theatre Institute, 1977-1978 (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 11)
    - Empire State Youth Theatre Institute, 1977-1979 (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 12)
    - Empire State Youth Theatre Institute, 1978 (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 13)
    - Empire State Youth Theatre Institute, 1981-1982 (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 14)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commissions, 1971 (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 15)
    - Federal Grants Report to Trustees, 1972 (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 16)
    - Financing Higher Education, 1972; Undated (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 17)
    - Hudson River Club, 1990 (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 18)
    - Long Island and the University, 1971 (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 19)
    - Loose letter and clipping, 1970-1973 (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 20)
    - Management Efficiency, Undated (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 21)
    - New York State Science and Technology Foundation / Batelle Institute, 1980-1981 (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 22)
    - New York State Science and Technology Foundation / Batelle Institute, 1981 (Box 7 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 23)
    - Planting Fields Arboretum property transfer, 1971 (Box 8 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 1)
    - Planting Fields Arboretum property transfer, 1971 (Box 8 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 2)
    - Progress Report to Presidents on Public Service, Undated (Box 8 (2-Series II:SUNY Administrative Records), Folder 3)